well thank you very much flat welcome
好，非常感谢您
everybody thanks for
大家谢谢
turning up my name is Josh long I'm the
出现我的名字是乔希，我是
developer advocate to the spring team at
春季团队的开发者拥护者
pivotal
关键的
okay we're going to talk about spring
好吧，我们要谈春天
boot and how to build beautiful
引导以及如何打造美丽
applications using spring boot for those
使用Spring Boot的应用程序
who don't know me I'm authoring or
谁不认识我，我正在创作或
different books think on brain to
不同的书思考着
different video series I'll commit on
我将继续制作不同的视频系列
several projects and I'm generally
几个项目，我通常
at your service so don't hesitate for
为您服务，所以不要犹豫
example at Starbucks man on Twitter and
推特上星巴克男人的例子
then there's my email just along its
然后是我的电子邮件
fingers back coamo J long at Philip
手指在菲利普长出Coamo J
it'll calm okay so um those of you have
会平静下来的，所以你们当中的那些人
been following the sort of industry the
一直在关注某种行业
last year so many will know that the
去年有很多人会知道
spring team moved to a new organization
春季团队搬到新的组织
called pivotal last year last April and
去年四月被称为关键
we joined a a larger family of similarly
我们加入了一个更大的家族
developer focused technologies uh you
以开发人员为中心的技术
know likes of class
知道喜欢上课
a foundry RabbitMQ Grails Tomcat reddits
铸造厂RabbitMQ Grails Tomcat Reddits
and of course spring not to mention the
当然，春天更不用说了
Hadoop distribution and young people so
Hadoop分布和年轻人如此
our mission is to simplify you know the
我们的任务是简化您知道的
development process for for developers
开发人员的开发过程
today and to help them build modern
今天并帮助他们建立现代
applications and we took out we took our
应用程序，我们拿出我们拿走了
mission heart because this is a new
使命之心，因为这是新事物
horizon a new opportunity we really want
展望我们真正想要的新机会
to do the best we could right by our
尽我们所能做到的最好
users so that that path took us a few
用户，以至于这条路带给我们一些
different places a first stop of course
不同地方当然是第一站
was our website we redesigned it it's a
是我们的网站，我们重新设计了
brand new website expose bring that I oh
全新网站曝光带来的我哦
that's the new home of spring on the web
那是网络上春天的新家
the application that runs on spring
在Spring上运行的应用程序
Denio is itself a spring boot
Denio本身就是 spring boot
application it's open source it's
它是开源的应用程序
available on github is under project
github上可用的项目
sagan and while i you know while i could
萨根，虽然我你知道我可以
go on about a lot of the other features
继续讲很多其他功能
on the website my favorite feature is a
在网站上，我最喜欢的功能是
DD guy
DD家伙
the guys on the website all 10 to 15
网站上的所有10至15个人
minutes long introductions to various or
分钟之久的各种介绍
types of application vertical that's a
垂直的应用程序类型
workload so if I want to build a REST
工作量，所以如果我想建立一个REST
API rest endpoint I can follow the guy
我可以跟随API的其他端点
that will teach me all work with a
那会教我所有的工作
messaging system or message broker like
消息传递系统或消息代理，例如
RabbitMQ the guys for that if I want to
RabbitMQ的家伙，如果我想
work with a no sequel or not only sequel
没有续集或不只是续集
or you know big data type of system such
或者您知道系统的大数据类型
as a no-see-um
不见面
neo4j or we could be there are guys as
neo4j或我们可能会有人
well so you know generally it's a good
好，所以您一般都知道这是一个很好的选择
place to get started to learn how to
开始学习如何
work with the spring technologies and of
与春季技术合作
course most so these guys are also good
当然最棒，所以这些家伙也很好
so lots of them sort of great things to
所以他们很多很棒的事情
look at in to read into and follow along
看着阅读并跟随
to kind of get a feel for what spring
有点春天的感觉
boot in today of course will we'll be
今天启动，我们当然会
looking at spring boot as well spring
看着 spring boot 还有春天
boot is
引导是
a focusing of attention it's a single
集中注意力是一个单一的
place where developers can stop it's a
开发人员可以阻止它的地方
place where they can start and consume
他们可以开始消费的地方
the rest of the what we call spring ask
我们称之为春季的其余部分
form so if you look at this architecture
形式，所以，如果你看这个架构
diagram is that top layer top level the
图是顶层顶层
IO execution layer that describes our
IO执行层描述了我们
three sort of entry points into the
进入的三种入口点
platform spring XD of course is our term
平台弹簧XD当然是我们的术语
key big data solution Grails is our
关键的大数据解决方案Grails是我们的
rapid application development centric
快速的以应用程序开发为中心
web framework and with a you know very
网络框架，并且您非常了解
strong movie focus and that spring boot
强大的电影焦点和那个 spring boot
is our sort of general purpose the entry
是我们的通用目的
point into the spring frameworks what
指出 Spring Framework
you would think of as the different
你会认为与众不同
spring frameworks we have those spring
春天的框架，我们有那些春天
frameworks representativeness and all
框架代表性和所有
foundation box here different libraries
基础箱在这里不同的图书馆
different frameworks that you would
您将要使用的不同框架
consume on the top levels on the Iowa
在爱荷华州的顶级消费
excuse me but you're looking at our
对不起，你在看我们
different technologies themselves long
长期以来，不同的技术本身
prophecy right so the distinction here
预言权，所以这里的区别
is one is well you know they exit the
是一个很好，你知道他们退出了
foundation grants been going to consume
基金会的赠款将要消耗掉
by running process and the executioner
通过运行流程和执行者
will actually launch process a process
实际上将启动一个过程
of course I mean more or less
我的意思是或多或少
corresponds to a thread or page or
对应于线程或页面或
company that um so spring boot it again
那个让春天重新启动的公司
we're we want people to be able to
我们希望人们能够
consume all these pieces to consume the
消耗所有这些碎片来消耗
API is there available in the spring oil
弹簧油中有API
platform without having to worry too
平台也不必担心
much about what goes where and how to
关于如何去哪里以及如何去做
tie it together not having to understand
绑在一起，不必理解
too much of
太多
too much of what's required to wire
接线太多了
everything up yeah the idea if you can
一切都很好，如果可以的话
pick it you know what you can imagine it
选择它，你知道你能想象得到什么
is what would it be like if you could
如果可以的话会是什么样
have arrogant Haller you know the core
有傲慢的哈勒，你知道核心
guy and the sprinkler mark the lead
家伙和洒水器标志着领先
Spring Framework
Spring Framework
committer what would it be like if you
提交者，如果你会是什么样
can have him sitting behind you over
可以让他坐在你后面
your shoulder you know guiding you on
你的肩膀，你知道指导你
your on what you're building as a
您正在建立的
building application um you'd probably
构建您可能会使用的应用程序
get a lot done a lot quicker right if
如果可以的话，可以更快地完成很多工作
you homeboy kind of insight and so the
你的男生有点洞察力，所以
idea is we want to codify that to put it
想法是我们要整理一下
in up there so place where basically you
在那里，基本上你在哪里
do you do actually have something like
你真的有类似的东西吗
him dying you right you do have the
他快死了，你确实有
wisdom and experience reflected in your
智慧和经验体现在您的
code booth is that wisdom it's it's it's
代码亭是智慧，是
our opinion it's our guidance on how to
我们的意见是我们如何
build types of applications we we
建立我们的应用程序类型
express those opinions through sensible
通过明智的表达意见
faults that you can rely on when you
您可以依靠的错误
build your applications so while boot
构建您的应用程序，以便在启动时
may sound like it's about boots Stephan
听起来像是斯蒂芬的靴子
what about boot strapping it's just
那绑靴子呢
about reducing conceptual overhead right
关于减少概念性开销权
conceptual baggage so with that kind of
这样的概念行李
explanation out of the way let us turn
解释让我们转向
toward more toward heavier topics what
朝向更重的话题
can we do with boot how can we use it
我们可以用启动做些什么，如何使用它
what can it be used for you know and how
它可以用于您的知识以及如何使用
can we change the world with it there
我们可以在那里改变世界吗
are a lot of good answers I confess I
我承认我有很多好的答案
didn't really find a very great one but
并没有真正找到一个很棒的，但是
what we're going to talk about today is
我们今天要谈论的是
how to build an engine that dough defies
如何制造一个面团抗拒的引擎
if you will different photos right so
如果您要不同的照片，那么
dos for those of you who don't want a
为那些不想
meme it's this Japanese blog pictured
模因这是这张日本博客
here that people have made sport of by
人们在这里运动
you know adding nonsensical explanations
你知道添加荒谬的解释
and texts and so on and then pairing
和文字等，然后配对
that with a cute picture of this very
一张非常可爱的照片
very very cute dog so what we want to do
非常非常可爱的狗，所以我们想做什么
is build an engine that automates that
是建立一个引擎
process
处理
I spent five minutes photoshopping in
我花了五分钟在
the image when you can spend an hour
您可以花一个小时的图像
what will quote to do it for you so
有什么报价可以为您做到
we're going to build this application
我们将构建此应用程序
today and in so doing will actually look
今天，这样做实际上看起来
a lot a lot of different pieces that
很多不同的东西
spring brings it to the table the way to
春天把它带到餐桌上的方式
work is it will take as input a photo
工作是将照片作为输入
depicts on the left and then we can add
在左侧进行描绘，然后我们可以添加
to that nonsensical exclamations of Lao
对老挝的荒谬感叹
such a grump etc along with a spring
这样的脾气等等，还有春天
door seal of approval and put it all
批准并盖上所有门封
together in a composite which you can
在一起，你可以
then extract on the other end of the
然后在另一端提取
proper if you want to see all this stuff
如果您想看到所有这些东西，那就合适
happening you will log into the monitor
碰巧您将登录监视器
applicate so two different end points
适用于两个不同的终点
two different views here one lets you
这里有两种不同的视图，一种可以让您
upload files and those one lets you you
上传文件，这些文件可以让您
know watch what's happening and see it
知道看发生了什么并看到它
happening and to see all the new updated
发生，并看到所有新的更新
images of their happen so this actually
他们发生的图像，所以这实际上
get started let's actually do that there
开始吧，让我们实际上在那里做
are a couple ways to get started with
有两种入门方法
boot the first one is of course just
引导第一个当然是
start that spring that'll start that
从那春天开始
spring that iowa ism
爱荷华州的春天
is just that it's a great it's a web
只是很棒，这是一个网络
service you can go there and just tell
服务，你可以去那里，只是告诉
the form you see fields here you know
您在此处看到字段的表格
that reflect the usual suspects or maven
反映出通常的嫌疑人或行家
project group idea the the artifact idea
项目组构想工件构想
the name of the project description the
项目名称描述
packages etc and then you have check
包等，然后您有检查
boxes and these check boxes and then
框和这些复选框，然后
these don't quote these correspond to
这些不引用这些对应
types of application workloads they
他们的应用程序工作负载类型
don't correspond to specific
不符合特定
technologies at least we don't want them
技术，至少我们不想要它们
to right we want them one typical thing
说对了，我们要他们做一件事
commodities from the broader strokes and
大范围的商品和
a specific framework technology so
一种特定的框架技术
suppose I want to build a web
假设我要建立一个网站
application check the web tier checkbox
应用程序选中“ Web层”复选框
suppose I want to work with the or for
假设我想与或合作
sequel and you know a natural natural
续集，你知道自然
fit there's J pool so just choose JPA
适合那里的J池，所以只需选择JPA
again right and I'm gonna I'm giving a
再次正确，我要给
zip file which I can unzip and you know
我可以解压缩的zip文件，您知道
start working with this works with
开始与此一起工作
anything right it's just a standard
任何正确的事情只是一个标准
maven build or a standard Gradle build
Maven构建或标准Gradle构建
if you like you can open it up in any
如果您愿意，可以在任何位置打开它
IDE of your choosing of course there's
您选择的IDE当然有
no magic here just open it up
这里没有魔术只是打开它
standard maven but we're going to use
标准的行家，但我们要使用
STF STF is our open source eclipse
STF STF是我们的开源日食
distribution and represent the superset
分布并代表超集
of the latest in greatest Java EE
最新的Java EE
distribution so at all times you'll have
分布，所以在任何时候都可以
everything in very stable quite plus a
一切都非常稳定相当加上
lot of extra great stuff and when I say
很多额外的好东西，当我说
extra stuff I mean for example that STS
我是说多余的东西，例如STS
had preliminary Java 8 support in
初步拥有Java 8支持
Eclipse
日食
full six months before regular Clips had
比常规剪辑快六个月
it for example or STS had preliminary
例如它或STS有初步
Gradle support long time before it was
Gradle支持很久以前
generally available in Eclipse so
通常在Eclipse中可用，因此
there's a lot of good stuff your typical
典型的好东西很多
stuff that people climbing for clamoring
人们为求欢而爬的东西
for but it hasn't been it hasn't made it
因为，但不是因为它没有做到
into the main projects yet
进入主要项目
now in STS
现在在STS
there are some really handy tools for
有一些非常方便的工具
example if you go to file new spring
例如，如果您要提交新的春季
starter project you're given a wizard it
入门项目，您会得到一个向导
looks familiar right I would imagine
看起来很熟悉，我想像中
this is the same wizard that you know
这就是你所知道的向导
basically it's the same wizard that we
基本上是与我们相同的向导
just looked at for you choose different
只是看着你选择不同
types of
种类
demo one area you choose the type of a
演示一个区域，您选择一个区域的类型
protocol that you want to local travel
您要本地旅行的协议
JPA and web choose it you know specify
JPA和Web选择您知道的指定
the group in the artifact etc next and
接下来是工件中的组，然后
you can see the actual URL the URL in
您可以看到网址中的实际网址
this text box is assume you all taste
这个文本框假设大家都喜欢
into the work into a browser to get that
进入浏览器进行工作
generated a zip file containing a build
生成了一个包含构建的zip文件
and some preliminary source code it's
还有一些初步的源代码
the same URL so this UI dialog is just a
相同的网址，因此此用户界面对话框只是
front-end for that web service so I
该Web服务的前端，所以我
usually wouldn't it doesn't really
通常不是真的
matter
物
I've already got a simple sort of
我已经有一个简单的
example there so
这样的例子
well actually I don't care I'll go ahead
好吧，其实我不在乎，我会继续
and do that so let's see so I'm going to
并这样做，让我们来看一下，我将
go ahead and choose demo one who's web
继续并选择一个演示者，谁是网络
hold on because JPA I'll go next
坚持，因为JPA，我下一步去
Big Finish
大完成
and we'll see here I've got a fairly
我们会在这里看到我有一个相当
sort of
有点
uninteresting
没意思
MV test class again nothing particularly
MV测试课再没什么特别的
special I've got a default empty
特别是我有一个默认的空
property file
属性文件
have an application class this
有一个应用程序类
application class it's just an entry
应用程序类，它只是一个入口
point it's just as public static void
就像公共静态无效一样
main and public static void main is one
main和public static void main是一个
all through the spring application that
在整个春季申请中
run method this is a spring boot
运行方法，这是一个 spring boot
specific class it in turn returns a
特定的类，它依次返回一个
reference to the spring application
参考弹簧应用
context so you just go here
上下文，所以你就去这里
and you can assign that right again you
您可以再次分配该权限
should usually need to deal with the
通常应该处理
application context but it's nice to
应用程序上下文，但很高兴
know that there's a very convenient way
知道有很方便的方法
to get it if you like so what we're
得到它，如果你喜欢我们是什么
doing is we're saying to spring okay
我们正在说春天好吗
create an application context take as
创建一个应用程序上下文
your initial input the the application
您最初输入的应用程序
class itself springing boot will
类本身会启动
discover that your regular spring
发现你定期的春天
annotations like the at configuration
像at配置这样的注释
annotation signal signal witness to add
注解信号见证人添加
this class could be a beam definition of
该类可能是梁的定义
configuration class there's the add
配置类有添加
components can annotation will bring to
可以注释的组件将带来
find all B's annotate with so-called
找到所有B的注释
stereo publications in the package that
包装中的立体声出版物
we're in right now or a deeper one and
我们现在或更深一层
register them as beans so this is just
将它们注册为bean，所以这仅仅是
typical component scanning and then
典型的组件扫描然后
finally we have the spring boot at
终于我们有了 spring boot
enable Auto configuration annotation
启用自动配置注释
this annotation tells spring boot that
这个注释告诉Spring Boot
we would like in to on our behalf based
我们想代表我们
on whatever it can infer from looking at
从它可以推断出的一切
path path open spring being context and
路径路径打开春天是上下文和
from the environment and anything else
来自环境和其他任何东西
that it has a visibility into to do
它具有要做的可见性
whatever it can to remove work from my
尽一切可能从我的工作中删除
path to give me sensible defaults and
给我合理的默认值的路径
this is the magic right this is where we
这就是神奇的权利，这就是我们
we really really win this because spring
我们真的赢得了这场胜利，因为春天
is going to do where it can to give a
会尽其所能
sensible default and do that to just
明智的默认设置，并做到这一点
break a little Java configuration we'll
打破一些Java配置，我们将
look at that a little bit later for now
稍后再看
with that other way let's actually turn
用另一种方式让我们实际上转向
to now to a sort of more sophisticated
到现在更复杂
version of a chain codebase I already
链代码库的版本我已经
gutted the bulk of the code and we're
删除了大部分代码，我们
going to go ahead and rebuild it up I
我要去重建它
won't bore you with all the details on
不会让您无聊的所有细节
one thing you should know though is when
你应该知道的一件事是什么时候
we look at this build file where they
我们看一下这个构建文件
they simple started what we looked at
他们简单地开始了我们的研究
earlier even the build file is sort of
甚至连构建文件都差不多
an opinionated way of solving a certain
解决某个问题的自以为是的方法
kind of problem right which is that of
一种问题权是
dependency meant so um first our bill
依赖意味着首先是我们的账单
pile just you know it points to a parent
一堆就知道你指向父母
build in this case one provided by
在这种情况下，由
spring boots that parent
那个父母的 spring boot
has managed the diversions of dependency
处理了依赖的转移
across all the major spring projects and
在所有主要的春季项目中
then it has also managed the versions of
然后它还管理了
dependencies that those spring projects
那些春季项目的依赖
are likely to use to need or use alright
可能需要使用或使用好
so again if I need a hibernate or if I
再说一次，如果我需要休眠或者如果我
need a logging a player depending again
需要记录一个球员再次
there's probably a version that's
可能有一个版本
already specified with air pump moving
空气泵移动时已指定
down a little bit you can see there are
下来一点，你可以看到有
three different dependencies here one is
三种不同的依赖关系之一是
a test dependency which is strictly
严格的测试依赖
speaking for test code and that's just
讲测试代码，那仅仅是
there by default and then otherwise you
那里默认情况下，然后你
have two different dependencies these
这些有两个不同的依赖性
two different dependencies correspond
两个不同的依赖项对应
roughly to the checkboxes that we
大致到我们的复选框
selected organism we selected web
我们选择了网络的选定生物
support as we got off or the spring
我们下车或春天时的支持
framework that boot spring boots starter
引导 spring boot 启动器的框架
web the penalty and we also selected
网络罚款，我们还选择了
that we want a police report we got a
我们想要警察报告，我们得到了
little spring permit boot spring mood
小小的春天准许引导春天的心情
starters data J plays these dependencies
入门数据J发挥了这些依赖性
are already ate a change in the status
已经吃了状态的改变
quo from what you won't be familiar with
从您不熟悉的地方
in the spring world if you think about
在春天的世界，如果你想一想
the spring or M module that module
弹簧或M模块
supports for example JDO and JPA one and
例如支持JDO和JPA
two and hibernate two three and four and
二和休眠二三和四和
you know JDBC etc so there's a lot of
你知道JDBC等，所以有很多
different pieces there and if that build
不同的部分在那里，如果那建立
effect you know that dependency had all
效果，您知道依赖已全部
of the types that it depended on you
取决于您的类型
know if it had those types marked as
知道它是否被标记为
anything but optional it would all be
除了可选以外的任何东西都将是
transitively important to become it be
暂时重要
very quickly a just sort of a really
很快，
really painful ugly mess you wouldn't
真的很痛苦，丑陋的混乱，你不会
want having 8 3 &amp; 4 &amp; JD or n people
想要有8 3＆4＆JD或n个人
support you know and all these different
支持您知道的所有这些不同
libraries on your classes at the same
同一班上的图书馆
time it'd be mayhem
时间会很混乱
you know what craziness should be dogs
你知道狗应该疯狂吗
and cats living together is my favorite
和猫在一起生活是我的最爱
line well
排好
so you know it's to be avoided right
所以你知道应该避免
that's what we're doing here is very
这就是我们在这里要做的
different what we're saying us for a a
与我们所说的不同
dependency that also that will support
也将支持的依赖
JPA workloads this is a well-known wall
JPA工作负载，这是众所周知的墙
tension world integrated staff this is
紧张世界综合人员，这是
not the kitchen sink this is just what
不是厨房的水槽，这就是
you need to get for me and it's
你需要为我而努力
reasonable it's a portable stuff it
合理，这是便携式的东西
you're not going to want to have to
您将不需要
think about later right so again this is
再想一想，所以这是
a fully fleshed-out stack but it is a
充实的堆栈，但这是一个
focused back we're not trying to support
集中精力，我们不试图支持
every permutation of day access here
每天访问的每个排列
with all the support for well-known
在所有知名度的支持下
stack in this case you're going to get
在这种情况下，您将获得
hybrid eight you're going to get a GPA
混合八，您将获得GPA
you're going to get you know the spring
你将使你知道春天
the requisite spoon modules and so on
必需的勺子模块等
again the same thing appear for the
同样的事情出现了
world we get all these pieces with that
世界，我们得到了所有这些碎片
one tiny little opinionated dependency
一个小小的自以为是的依赖
you'll note that we don't have any
您会注意到我们没有任何
inversions here all right
这里的反转好
these versions again the managed by the
这些版本再次由
parent palm and the implication is that
父掌，其含义是
if you know and say a couple years time
如果你知道并说几年的时间
for example spring boot who knows
例如 spring boot ，谁知道
two or three or whatever well if that
两个或三个，如果这样的话
version comes along with home via the
版本通过
version here it's fair to assume that
这里的版本可以假设
the versions that are managed by the
由...管理的版本
pirate palm will also get upgraded right
海盗手掌也将正确升级
you'll also see those up and that's a
你也会看到那些，那是一个
that's a big win because you're no
那是一个巨大的胜利，因为你不是
longer in charge of certifying that that
负责证明
these pieces of work together an extreme
这些工作一起极端
late
晚的
well it should just work right so it
好吧，它应该工作正常，所以它
should be a lot easier to move any
移动任何东西都应该容易得多
version again again this is not even you
再次版本，这甚至不是你
know we're not even here to talk about
知道我们甚至不在这里谈论
maven dependencies but it's just one
Maven的依赖，但这只是一个
really nice nice touches that exemplify
真的很好很好的例子
life spring boot that makes it very easy
生活 spring boot ，使其非常容易
to to move quicker you know okay moving
要更快地移动，你知道可以移动
to code now now that we've got an
现在进行编码，我们已经有了
understanding for what a basic project
了解什么是基本项目
looks like we're going to return to this
看起来我们要回到这个
spring dose project and we're going to
春季剂量项目，我们将要
build that application that we described
构建我们描述的应用程序
earlier something to those your five
早点给你的五个人
images I suppose in that natural first
我想自然而然的图像
step in this case is to worry about data
这种情况下的步骤是担心数据
access right we're going use MongoDB
访问权，我们将使用MongoDB
because
因为
why not you know MongoDB is a perfectly
为什么不知道MongoDB是完美的
fine instrument for storing data I've
我已经存储数据的好工具
got a little cheat sheet here I've got
这里有一些备忘单，我有
some classes and code already written so
一些类和代码已经写好了
too
太
coil typing it all up in time so we're
线圈及时输入所有内容，因此我们
going to have a simple dough modeling
将有一个简单的面团模型
user and then the usual commands going
用户，然后执行通常的命令
to end photos we're going to store the
结束照片，我们将存储
photos on monkey with a FX file system
带有FX文件系统的猴子上的照片
this is a natural fit for those or kind
这是自然适合的人
of builds cloud or Pat you know past
构建云或帕特，你过去知道
platform over for a full aware type
完全了解类型的平台
applications were often there is no
应用程序通常没有
durable hard disk so we're going to
耐用的硬盘，所以我们要
build first the user entity okay
首先建立用户实体好
you
您
and paste that in there
并粘贴到那里
and you can see I've got an annotation
你会看到我有一个注释
the annotation comes from from spring
注释来自春天
beta Mangal it's an annotation that it
beta Mangal是它的注释
is a lightweight or am mapping do well
是轻量级还是贴图效果很好
we're saying to spring day among go that
我们说到春天去
we want this object to represent a be
我们希望这个对象代表一个
fun structure you know resize it which
您知道有趣的结构，请调整大小
is the binary JSON format among leaders
是领导者之间的二进制JSON格式
we want this to represent the data in
我们要用它来表示数据
what will collections in a user's
用户的收藏品将是什么
collection if you will and we want this
收集，如果您愿意，我们想要这个
field to be used as the index or the tea
用作索引或茶的字段
obviously the annotation means different
显然，注释意味着不同
things in different contexts if you're
如果您是在不同背景下的事情
using a spring data gem fire Springs
使用spring数据gem fire springs
Adel you know Redis or spring data you
Adel，您知道Redis或Spring数据，
know 4j either you'll have a different
知道4j要么你会有不同
set where appropriate okay that's a
设置适当的地方
simple user and as I mentioned each user
简单的用户，正如我提到的每个用户
will manage one to end photos so we'll
将管理一张结束照片，因此我们将
have a type to describe a dovish photos
具有描述鸽形照片的类型
okay add a class soon
好的，请尽快添加课程
it's
它的
voila so we have now a Doge photo which
瞧，我们现在有一张总督照片
has an index and ID and it has a pointer
有一个索引和ID，并且有一个指针
to the user that contains it right so
给包含它的用户吧
this is the a collection that contains a
这是一个包含
the photo data and then in the photo
照片数据，然后在照片中
data always all the name of the file for
数据始终是文件的所有名称
the for the photo that can be looked up
用于可以查找的照片
on looked upon the credit fest files
在看信用节文件
people model well but those you know
人们建模很好，但是你知道的
we've got two entities now we've got two
我们有两个实体现在我们有两个
different details or objects that can
不同的细节或物体可以
not be mapped to the records of the
没有映射到
Davis
戴维斯
we now need some actual way to do that
我们现在需要一些实际的方法来做到这一点
method actually execute the queries and
方法实际上执行查询，
will leads in the updates and deletes
将导致更新和删除
and so on and in most systems that
等等，在大多数系统中
corresponds to the the repository there
对应那里的存储库
right so repository is a natural vehicle
是的，所以存储库是自然的工具
for crud style code so I'm going to
原始样式代码，所以我要
create a those photo repository a
创建一个照片库
repository for dealing with doors for
处理门的仓库
them I'm going to do that by building on
他们我将通过建立
top of springdale repository spring data
Springdale存储库 spring data 顶部
repository support repositories map more
仓库支持仓库映射更多
or less to the idea of active record
或少于主动记录的想法
object in Ruby and rails right there
Ruby和Rails中的对象
they're convenient ways to based on
它们是基于
convention create you know finders crew
惯例创建您认识发现者的工作人员
you know create meet sound records here
你知道在这里创建见面记录
we're defining an interface and the
我们正在定义一个接口，
interface extend the spring did a manga
界面延长弹簧做了漫画
repository right we've typed it to those
仓库权，我们已经将其键入到那些
photo and string where those photo is
照片和这些照片所在的字符串
the type of entity that we want to
我们想要的实体类型
manipulate string is the type of the
操作字符串是
index for that entity so what we're
该实体的索引，所以我们
saying is we want to create a repository
就是我们要创建一个存储库
that we played those photo entities and
我们扮演了那些照片实体，
also wish for the photo until you have
也希望照片，直到你有
an ID field at self type string you kind
您喜欢的自类型字符串的ID字段
of click around you can see the number
的点击次数可以看到数字
of Pi polar based then defines different
基于Pi Polar的定义
method for Faden querying different
Faden查询不同方法
types of data insert number this
数据插入编号的类型
interface then extends the paging
接口然后扩展分页
inserting the particle along in that
在其中插入粒子
interface you'll find methods for
界面，您将找到用于
finding all of a given type and file all
查找所有给定类型并全部归档
the details etc and of course in that
细节等，当然
you'll find the a Quadra pause boy which
您会发现一个Quadra暂停男孩
you'll find the methods for saving
您会找到保存方法
entity for saving many other finding of
用于保存许多其他发现的实体
one by its ID it's right so very common
一个通过其ID是正确的，因此非常常见
case is already well supported and note
案例已经得到很好的支持，请注意
that we haven't written any quote all
我们还没有写任何报价
we've done left bar is written in an
我们已经完成了左栏写在
interface that extend the network but no
扩展网络但没有接口
implementation we're going to do the
实施，我们将要做
same thing for our user goal oh okay you
对于我们的用户目标，同样的事情，哦，好
use a repository
使用仓库
like so
像这样
you
您
okay paste that in
好吧，粘贴在
Wow
哇
there you go we've got two different
你去那里我们有两个不同的
repositories that can be used in the
可以在
event or different entities making short
事件或其他实体做空
work of all the create we can update
我们可以更新的所有创作的工作
using style logic that most people spend
使用大多数人花费的风格逻辑
a lot of home rolling this is
很多本垒打是
boilerplate stuff this is stuff that you
样板的东西，这是你的东西
shouldn't have to write so so don't you
不应该写，所以你不是
know what's been data there's it's
知道数据是什么
really not a it's really not hard to
真的不是，这真的不难
avoid
避免
writing all that stuff
写所有的东西
um with that and way out of the way we
嗯，这与我们的出路
can actress exploring new are
可以女演员探索新
repositories to install some sample data
存储库以安装一些示例数据
some test data so I've got here a simple
一些测试数据，所以我在这里很简单
beam definition for an initializing beam
初始化光束的光束定义
using Java 8 in this example and in some
在此示例和某些示例中使用Java 8
8 you have lambda expressions lambda
8你有lambda表达式lambda
expressions are assignable to instances
表达式可分配给实例
of interfaces that are so-called
所谓的接口
functional interfaces that is they are
它们是功能接口
said to have one abstract method in this
说有一个抽象方法
case
案件
initializing beam is a fun people by
初始化梁是一个有趣的人
default right so it's an interval with
默认权限，所以这是一个间隔
one an implanted method
一种植入方法
recall that in Java 8 you have default
回想一下，在Java 8中，您具有默认值
methods in interfacing so I used it I
接口的方法，所以我用了
use the distinction one abstract method
使用区别一种抽象方法
for read it you can have an interface
阅读它，你可以有一个界面
with 10 methods but none of them could
有10种方法，但没有一种可以
be default and so the rule still applies
是默认值，因此该规则仍然适用
you can still assign a lambda expression
您仍然可以分配lambda表达式
to that interface as we are here so this
到我们在这里的界面，所以这
is a lambda expression the body inside
是体内的lambda表达
the curly brackets is eventually pushed
大括号最终被推
inside of a class that implements within
在内部实现的类中
a sledding beam interface and then that
横梁界面，然后
is returned as the FB ads with all Java
作为所有Java的FB广告返回
configuration this is a Java
配置这是一个Java
configuration beam definition provider
配置梁定义提供程序
and there is the class of the baby pink
还有婴儿粉的类
living being interface the dependency
生活界面的依赖
that this being needs to be a quirk are
这需要成为一个怪癖是
enumerated as arguments for wall for the
枚举为墙的参数
factory method itself so here we're
工厂方法本身，所以在这里
saying spring I need a pointer to the
说春天，我需要一个指向
usual polyfill a bit I don't care where
通常的填充有点我不在乎
you get it just find it funny by point
你得到它只是发现它有趣一点
and of course that's going to find the
当然可以找到
implementation of the interface that
接口的实现
we've just defined for you today with
今天我们刚刚为您定义了
that in place we can save data right so
这样我们就可以保存数据了
I've got three to records I'm going to
我有三个要记录的记录
save here add an amazing author sire
保存在此处添加一位了不起的作家父亲
and so and Phil webs up here of course
因此，Phil当然会在这里上网
either the two co-leads for spring boot
spring boot 的两个共同负责人
thank you gentlemen
谢谢先生们
and then down here I'm going to query
然后在这里我要查询
all the records in the navy and
海军的所有记录和
enumerate them I'm going to just have
列举他们，我将只拥有
I'm going to use the collection the new
我将使用新的收藏
methods in the collection interface to
收集接口中的方法
iterate over every record and then call
遍历每条记录，然后调用
based on this method reference the print
根据此方法参考打印
line method for every object that's all
每个对象的行方法
this is going to it's going to pass X
这将通过X
for each X in 3 and different places and
对于3个不同位置的每个X，
then pass X to the system error print
然后将X传递给系统错误打印
line method and okay so with that other
行方法，好的，其他
way then see if we you know we've made
然后看看我们是否知道我们做了
progress go ahead and start the
前进，开始
application
应用
off to a good start I don't know if you
开个好头，我不知道你是否
saw that interphase bringing the FP art
看到中间阶段带来了FP艺术
up there but that's important
在那里，但这很重要
you are that is some good still maybe
你是那还是不错的，也许
it's not actually that important that
其实并不重要
Irene want it um and then then here as
艾琳想要它，然后在这里
we as promised you'll see here that we
我们保证您会在这里看到我们
have system that aired you know put mine
有播出的系统，您知道把我的
so what we're doing is we're sending to
所以我们要做的是发送到
system error every record in the
系统错误中的每条记录
database and in this case the three
数据库，在这种情况下是三个
records here and then print a nap and
记录在这里，然后打个and
you can already know we've got you know
你已经知道我们知道了
if you look at if you actually look
如果你看，如果你真的看
there's pretty navigation on a regular
定期导航很漂亮
POSIX terminal modern one probably
POSIX终端现代可能
it supports cutters there's some very
它支持刀具，有一些非常
very very sensible defaults for even for
非常非常明智的默认值
everything including login so by default
包括登录在内的所有内容，因此默认情况下
logging is not very aggressive and it's
日志记录不是很积极，它是
well colored well file it's very easy to
颜色很好的文件非常容易
glanced at from afar and kind of parse
从远处看了一眼，并分析了一下
the information by the shapes and colors
通过形状和颜色获得的信息
of the text doesn't overwhelm you with
的文字不会让您不知所措
just noise you know
只是你知道的声音
okay so we're often we we've made good
好吧，所以我们经常做的很好
progress here we've got a working data
进度这里我们有一个工作数据
tier up and running we've got three
分层运行，我们有三个
didn't record to the database now what
现在没有记录到数据库
we need to build a service something
我们需要建立某种服务
that will consume repositories something
会消耗存储库的东西
that'll expose coarse-grain business
这将暴露粗粒度的业务
operations to the client so create this
对客户端的操作，因此创建此
class here
在这里上课
doors
门
Ernest
欧内斯特
you
您
and of course I'm going to just go ahead
当然，我要继续
and grab the bits for that here
并在这里抓住一点
you
您
and what you have is a regular spring
而你有一个定期的春天
room and a table have service so it will
房间和桌子有服务，所以它将
be picked up and they add components and
被捡起来，他们添加组件和
please that will open area and then it
请打开区域然后
in turn defines three different being
反过来定义了三个不同的存在
dependencies that it needs to be able to
需要具备的依赖性
do the cork and it has those injected
做软木塞，并注入那些
through press they're injecting anything
通过新闻界，他们正在注入任何东西
and on a wire then the constructor has
然后在电线上，构造函数有
evil through dependencies you know as
通过依赖而邪恶
let's construct argument and then you
让我们构造参数，然后
say you you'll find two different
说你会发现两个不同
methods one for reading and one for a
一种阅读方法，一种阅读方法
different types of photos
不同类型的照片
so these different types of photos well
所以这些不同类型的照片很好
you know again I restored on the MongoDB
你又知道我在MongoDB上恢复了
credit as file system we're going to use
我们将使用的信用为文件系统
the photo manipulator API which is a
照片操纵器API，它是
graphic Java on image buffer
图像缓冲区上的图形Java
manipulation program that we have
我们拥有的操纵程序
written off to the side here in the
在这里写到一边
spring Jewish photo module this is as I
春天的犹太照片模块，因为我
mentioned just make it odd you know
提到只是让你觉得奇怪
graphics code nothing particularly fancy
图形代码没什么特别花哨的
but I won't bore you with that right now
但我现在不会厌烦你
is nothing but the cycle and then
只是循环而已
finally we have a repository and same
终于我们有了一个资料库
postures we've created earlier and
我们之前创建的姿势和
that's not bad but of course it's very
不错，但是当然
hard to see that a service can be much
很难看到一项服务可以是很多
more natural you can expose it along
更自然，您可以将其暴露
with people have an even way of
与人有一种平等的方式
consuming it like rest or like HTTP so
像休息或HTTP一样使用它
the next level is to create a REST API I
下一个级别是创建一个REST API
like to hope that you know while most
希望您知道
people well while it has been said that
有人说，人们很好
a sophisticated API eventually sends
复杂的API最终会发送
email I like to joke that eventually a
我喜欢开玩笑的电子邮件，最终
significant if that sprout arrest
如果发芽停止，则意义重大
endpoint and that's what we're going to
端点，这就是我们要做的
do here going to sprout a weapon point
在这里要发芽的武器点
for our code so go to our controller
为我们的代码，所以去我们的控制器
package
包
Plus
加
users rest controller
用户 rest controller
you
您
a set in here
这里的一套
okay just choosing types here
好，只在这里选择类型
big
大
so
所以
or missing anything
或缺少任何东西
I am
我是
right wrong media type type
对错媒体类型类型
Oh lime
哦石灰
so
所以
well they should have a working
好吧，他们应该有一个工作
controller now yep and this controller
控制器现在是和这个控制器
is just a standard springing feed
只是标准的弹跳饲料
nesting Pole it's you can tell because
嵌套极点是因为
well it's annotated with address
好吧，上面有地址注释
controller the rest control annotation
控制器其余控件注释
signal between either this endpoint is
该端点之间的信号是
not your regular add controller but
不是您的常规添加控制器，而是
instead a rest controller was returned
而是返回了一个 rest controller
values should just be converted to
值应仅转换为
whatever content type is required by the
无论内容类型是
client using standard content
客户使用标准内容
negotiation right so this is in stark
谈判权，所以这很明显
contrast to a regular at controller
与常规at控制器形成对比
annotated bean whose return values have
带注释的bean，其返回值具有
to have the response body annotation if
具有响应主体注释，如果
they're if the payload is to be
他们是如果有效载荷是
converted right so again it's index
正确转换，因此再次是索引
sugar for something you can already very
糖的东西你已经可以很
only say for text annotation but still
只说文字注解，但仍然
there can be other than that not really
可能还有其他不是真的
a lot to look at here right you've got a
很多东西要看这里，你有一个
method for returning all the user data
返回所有用户数据的方法
you've got a method for uploading photos
您有一种上传照片的方法
you've got me looking for reading photos
你让我在看照片
etc so we could start we could deploy
等等，所以我们可以开始部署
this music start using curl but I think
这种音乐开始使用卷曲，但我认为
we owe ourselves better let's actually
我们应该欠我们自己
go ahead and see what we can do to give
继续前进，看看我们能做些什么
ourselves something more interactive
我们自己更具互动性
need a web application right we're
需要一个网络应用程序，我们
building from building web web
从建筑网建设
application that intern talks to a web
实习生与网络对话的应用程序
service
服务
you
您
so we'll go ahead and go ahead and
所以我们继续前进，继续前进，
depend on the spring doors web module
取决于弹簧门Web模块
the nice thing is if you look at our
好东西是，如果你看看我们的
palm that XML
掌控XML
we're just depending on this module that
我们只是依靠这个模块
this project the project itself you know
这个项目你知道的项目本身
it has the usual suspects for a web
它具有通常的网络嫌疑人
application for a client-side web
客户端Web应用程序
application it has your normal uh let's
应用程序，它具有您的正常状态，让我们
see so it's mainly a choice
看到所以这主要是一个选择
normal JavaScript and so on Seattle I'm
普通的JavaScript，等等，西雅图
using the power client-side JavaScript a
使用强大的客户端JavaScript
package manager here so all the
打包经理在这里，所有
JavaScript
的JavaScript
assets are neat involved with mid folder
资产与中间文件夹整齐
for me thank you
对我来说谢谢
amusing angular that chair of wealthy
有趣的那个富有的椅子的角度
people fallacy etc and then I've got a
人们的谬误等，然后我有一个
template spoken so by default spring
说的模板，因此默认情况下是spring
Boop look inside of source manual public
Boop在源手册public中的外观
and expose everything in there at the
并在那里暴露一切
root of the web application I'm gonna
Web应用程序的根目录
fall to the looking source main
落入寻找源头
resources templates and explore those
资源模板并进行探索
templates using whatever view is all
使用所有视图的模板
written in this case we're using the
在这种情况下，我们使用
time view engine time leaf is a natural
时间视图引擎时间叶是自然的
templating library the idea that you can
模板库，您可以
take a template make changes to it and
以模板对其进行更改，然后
then productionize it you know actually
然后生产它，你实际上知道
apply expressions and so on to to make
应用表达式等
it more dynamic and then give that same
它更具动态性，然后赋予相同的效果
page back to default you can have and
返回到默认页面，您可以拥有和
continue to retain design fidelity with
继续保持设计的忠诚度
the original design right this is in
这是原始设计权
stark contrast to something like PHP
与PHP之类的东西形成鲜明对比
which let's just be very
让我们变得非常
honest year jsps don't really lend
诚实的一年jsps并不真正放贷
themselves to design infidelity for lots
自己设计很多不忠
of reasons scriptlets are lonely
scriptlet寂寞的原因
insanely a pickier parser is another the
疯狂的pickier解析器是另一个
ticker so one solution in the Java
代码，所以是Java中的一种解决方案
community in Google's thing called time
Google称之为时间的社区
if it's fairly well liked that's a very
如果它相当受欢迎，那是一个非常
well liked as I mentioned exportation
正如我提到的出口一样受欢迎
five natural templates and and it
五个自然模板
happens to be very use of Springs so by
碰巧非常利用Springs，因此
both if spring detects and Tiny's type
如果检测到弹簧和Tiny的类型
of lap pad it will register that view is
的笔记本电脑将注册该视图是
over and that view ended for you
结束，该视图为您而结束
you
您
so what we have here our JavaScript
所以我们这里有我们的JavaScript
files and HTML files that are going to
文件和HTML文件
be exposed and made available through
暴露出来并通过
the web service here through the web
通过网络这里的网络服务
application
应用
the only thing I think I need to do now
我认为我现在唯一需要做的
is
是
routing right so I'm going to go ahead
路由正确，所以我要继续
and go back to the application class
回到应用程序类
register for a webinar and after and in
注册网络研讨会以及之后和之后
that registration I'm going to add view
该注册我要添加视图
controllers I'm going to basically map
我要映射的控制器
full-size client to the view name client
全尺寸客户端到视图名称客户端
which in this case force corresponds to
在这种情况下，力对应于
the timely view client that HTML same
HTML相同的及时查看客户端
deal for mine as well my HTML and point
以及我的HTML和点
um this will let us sort of work with a
嗯，这将使我们能够与
web application pick in this model
此模型中的Web应用程序选择
already we don't have to write all that
已经我们不必写所有这些了
separate so
所以分开
you
您
I've neglected to define a type of being
我忽略了定义存在的类型
here
这里
I forgot to define
我忘了定义
later mean that's required to drive the
后来意味着这是驱动
service so let's do that now
服务，所以现在就开始做吧
and Josh we just debug spring food
和乔希，我们只是调试春季食品
application
应用
standard Eclipse debugger yep you can
是的，您可以使用标准的Eclipse调试器
use them regular this is just standard
定期使用它们只是标准
Java you can use any editor any ID it's
Java，您可以使用任何编辑器的任何ID
a traitor
叛徒
you don't have to use eclipse there is a
您不必使用eclipse
handy dandy runners or debug as well
方便的花花公子奔跑者或调试
spring boo debt but all that does is it
春季嘘债务，但所有的是它
finds the entry point class which is a
找到入口点类
class with public static void main
具有public static void main的类
rather than relations and it runs if it
而不是关系，它会运行
even if you're on and it's not the point
即使你在路上也不是重点
please you will find the entry point and
请您找到入口点和
run it for you cool extra that question
运行它为您酷炫的那个问题
great question say they register that
好问题说他们注册
bean actually register to beans
bean实际上注册到bean
one two
一二
you
您
Theater java imagination manipulation
Theatre Java想象力操纵
moravia those photo manipulator and then
moravia那些照片操纵器，然后
another one here is a great combo this
这里的另一个是很棒的组合
is a spring data grid effect template it
是一个弹簧数据网格效果模板
is a web template object for working
是用于工作的Web模板对象
with the MongoDB file system API the
使用MongoDB文件系统API
great effects file file system that
伟大的效果文件系统
built on top of MongoDB and again we're
建立在MongoDB之上，我们再次
going to depend on things like the Mongo
取决于像蒙哥这样的东西
but you know the Mongo connection and we
但是你知道蒙哥的联系，我们
all know a little bit instance these are
都知道一点实例，这些是
two beans that have been defined
已经定义了两个bean
elsewhere by spring boot so we don't
spring boot 在其他地方，所以我们不
have to worry about how to get created
不得不担心如何创建
this is notable privately and they're
私下里这很明显，他们
usefully defaulted right so just default
有用的默认权限，所以默认
to Mongo instance make the localhost and
到Mongo实例使localhost和
connect to the database called test if I
如果我连接到名为test的数据库
were to define it being a pipe Mangal in
将其定义为管道Mangal
this application class
此应用程序类
then that being would be would begin
然后那个存在将开始
also we'd get a pointer to that one
我们也会得到一个指向
instead as opposed to the default one
而不是默认的
that gets created in the absence of some
在没有某些东西的情况下创建的
other
其他
bungabine so not to put too fine a head
邦加宾，所以不要把头太细
on it if I want to define my own bungle
如果我想定义自己的束缚
object and connect to some other
对象并连接到其他对象
database I can if not spring boot will
数据库，如果没有，我可以 spring boot
do it it's not that spring boot gets in
这样做不是不是 spring boot 进入了
the way if I'll be trying to help in
如果我要尝试帮助的方式
absence of some particular input from
缺少来自某些特定输入
you
您
with that I'll set up ready to go I can
这样我就可以开始准备了
go ahead and just run it as a spring
继续前进，就像春天一样
wood app by the way there is a very
顺便说一句木制应用程序
handy key command just a command 3 and
方便的按键命令只是命令3和
you'll find all sorts of great commands
您会发现各种各样的好命令
in it including debug spring boot
其中包括调试弹簧启动
application
应用
yup here
是的
what have I done now
我现在做了什么
you
您
let's make sure I have everything here
让我们确保我在这里拥有一切
those for a minute later with a test
一分钟后通过测试
template
模板
News
新闻
troller
拖钓者
ah
啊
couple things I've neglected here
我在这里忽略的几件事
I don't need this message dating
我不需要这个消息约会
temperat just yet
刚刚调温
got ahead of myself there Oh
领先于我自己哦
with that
接着就，随即
that out
那出来
you
您
I lent that out
我借出去了
three bye
三拜
you
您
there we are that looks more like it
那里我们看起来更像它
sorry about that I had a fun jacket
对不起，我穿了一件有趣的外套
unsatisfied beam dependency for a
光束对光束的不满意
messaging template and I needed that
消息传递模板，我需要
so our applications up and running we
因此我们的应用程序启动并运行
better print it out data and this is all
更好地将其打印出数据，这就是全部
here if we go to the browser localhost
在这里，如果我们转到浏览器本地主机
client like that you'll see that we get
这样的客户，您会看到我们得到
our fancy HTML file ball interface and
我们漂亮的HTML文件球界面和
again if we go to localhost clients
再一次，如果我们去本地客户端
monitor
监控
we get an empty page and the idea is
我们得到一个空白页，想法是
that this page this interim monitor page
该页面此临时监视页面
should show us the images that we've a
应该向我们展示我们拥有的图像
little only on the client on the left um
只在左边的客户端上很少
however it doesn't know when something
但是它不知道什么时候
has happened
已经发生了
I just client on the right this monitor
我只是在右边这台显示器的客户
on the right doesn't know with me on the
右边的我不知道
left and that implies a different
左，这意味着不同
problem we need some way of notifying
问题，我们需要一些通知的方式
the monitor that something has changed a
显示器发生了变化
natural way to do this is to use
自然的方法是使用
WebSockets and it turns out that
WebSockets，事实证明
WebSockets are very easy to do with
WebSockets非常易于使用
spring and that's with spring Boop I'll
春天，那是春天
go ahead and copy this again I've got a
继续复制一次，我有一个
cheat sheet here I'm going to go ahead
备忘单，我要继续
and register my M configuration for
并注册我的M配置
WebSocket close this down here
WebSocket在这里关闭
okay
好的
and all I'm doing them I'm using a
而我正在做的所有事情我都在使用
standard spring for WebSocket
WebSocket的标准弹簧
configuration and I'm just doing the
配置，我只是在做
part that spring boot couldn't possibly
spring boot 不可能的部分
get name am naming the end point and
获得名称是命名终点，
configuring the particular WebSocket
配置特定的WebSocket
support that I need from spring specific
从春季特定我需要的支持
to my application I'm saying I want to
对我的应用程序，我是说我想
add an in-point named O's on a label
在标签上添加一个名为O的点
faster than support softer gif is a a
比支持更柔和的gif更快
client-side JavaScript library and they
客户端JavaScript库，他们
form protocol it's a superset of avoid
表单协议是避免的超集
sockets if you will so when a client
套接字，如果你会这样当一个客户端
when the sausages Tomsk a plant connects
当香肠托木斯克的植物连接时
to a stop of this enabled service
停止此启用的服务
endpoint it will attempt to negotiate a
端点，它将尝试协商
WebSocket connection otherwise it'll
WebSocket连接，否则它将
gracefully degrade and support for
优雅降级并支持
example a polling or you know whatever a
例如投票，或者您知道
fallback alternative is this is very
后备替代方案是这是非常
useful for those browsers that quite
对于那些相当有用的浏览器
support the latest and greatest stuff I
支持我最新和最伟大的东西
won't I won't you know I won't reasons
我不会，你不会知道我不会理由
of modesty name names and pointing
谦虚的名字名字和指向
fingers but if I were to name names
手指，但如果我要命名
point fingers that browser like running
用手指指着浏览器喜欢跑步
with something like winter net explorer
像冬季网浏览器
again uses a modest history and when I
再次使用谦虚的历史，当我
won't point fingers or name names it's
不会指向手指或命名它的
beneath me I won't do that um I can't
在我下面我不会那样做，我不能
so with that you can play i configured
这样你就可以玩我配置
my WebSocket support and I my client
我的WebSocket支持和我的客户
side basically I'm going to say to my
基本上我要对我说
client listen for all messages and
客户端监听所有消息并
whenever a message comes in containing a
每当邮件中包含
URI that represents the new photo that's
代表新照片的URI
been uploaded go ahead and update the
已上传，请继续更新
end the the monitor page right
结束监控页面右
support that I actually need to send
我实际需要发送的支持
method from all over to go ahead and
从各地来的方法
reintroduce the bits I'd commented out
重新介绍我评论过的位
from the thing earlier this particular
从之前的事情开始
case they a bit where we actually send
如果他们有点我们实际发送
the message the notification to the
消息通知到
client informing it that via then the
客户端通知它
image has been uploaded so
图片已上传，因此
voila okay so now I have my resting
瞧，好，现在我休息了
folder and on file upload when the image
文件夹和文件上载时的图像
is uploaded I send a notification to
已上传，我向
topic for that alarm and I stand as my
该警报的主题，我站在我的面前
payload and object is given map then we
有效载荷和对象被赋予地图，然后我们
convert it to JSON and we'll have as its
将其转换为JSON，我们将其作为
field the keys in this map right that's
在此地图中列出关键
just a natural mapping and JSON till not
只是一个自然的映射和JSON，直到没有
and then since we've only got T and this
然后因为我们只有T和这个
one field we can use the singleton map
一个字段，我们可以使用单例地图
convenience that then the collection is
方便，然后收集
a class that comes with a JDK and so
JDK附带的类，因此
you're going to get a JSON structure
您将获得一个JSON结构
with the pool those are the photo URI at
在泳池里，这些是位于的照片URI
URI and then we're going to let the
URI，然后我们将让
client see that change an updated state
客户看到更改了更新状态
let's rerun the application
让我们重新运行应用程序
okay
好的
reload
重装
now we can try it out and see what we
现在我们可以尝试一下，看看我们
got here
去那里
here
这里
we'll start with
我们将从
we'll start with something you know we
我们将从你知道的东西开始
want to stress test as saying as best as
想要压力测试说得最好
we can so we'll bring to bear the full
我们可以，所以我们将承担全部
and awesome power of David Hasselhoff
和大卫·哈塞尔霍夫（David Hasselhoff）的强大力量
drag that image on to the air
将该图像拖到空中
happen on the left
发生在左边
oops I've got to configure multi-part
糟糕，我必须配置多部分
config
配置
so
所以
this is a 1fp I knew that here
这是1fp我知道在这里
they are
他们是
I need to tell spring boot where I want
我要告诉 spring boot 我要去哪里
to say it we know how much data I want
说出来，我们知道我想要多少数据
to enable to be uploaded so remember by
启用上传功能，因此请记住
default spring boots use a servlet 3
默认的 spring boot 使用servlet 3
environment and in that in that API you
环境，在那个API中
have the part if you had a server part
如果您有服务器部分，则有一部分
API to handle file uploads in lieu of
用于处理文件上传的API
something like for example common style
例如普通样式
upload
上载
here we're going to go ahead and just
在这里，我们将继续前进，只是
restart the application and so we're
重新启动应用程序，所以我们
saying is when files are uploaded we
就是说文件上传的时候
want to have a file no larger than 10
想要文件不大于10
Meg's otherwise rejected you can also
梅格否则拒绝您也可以
configure where's
配置哪里
you
您
job must yo-yo Tigers at the hop on the
工作必须溜溜虎跳上
right you do there for a second you
对，你在那里做一秒钟
might want to back up about one or two
可能要备份大约一两个
senses awkward you guys at least see the
感觉尴尬你们至少看到了
really really awesome part really lots
真的很棒真的很多
of brought to bear the full awesome
带来了令人敬畏的全力
pilot hop ok yes we only miss one or two
飞行员跳好吧，我们只错过一两个
sentences now where you have self
现在你有自我的句子
actualized it's okay - II saw that um
意识到还可以-我看到了那个
but you know we can also bring mr. Doge
但是你知道我们也可以带先生来。总督
himself right so drag and drop over
自己正确，所以拖放
there and you yeah the Doge affiant
在那里，你是总督的亲戚
version of delicious oh look at that
版好吃喔看那个
even a captions also that's food that's
甚至字幕也就是食物
all so okay we've got a basic working
很好，我们已经完成了基本工作
web application for its kind of web
网络应用程序
application babysitting a daemon that
保姆守护程序
was assembled here from you know very
是从你那里组装的
few pieces very quickly we didn't have
很快我们就没有了几块
to we didn't have to configure same data
我们不必配置相同的数据
we didn't have to configure SCIM you see
我们不必配置看到的SCIM
you have to configure well almost
您几乎必须配置好
anything really we have to configure
我们必须配置的所有内容
things that spring boot couldn't
spring boot 做不到的事情
possibly know about for example the
可能知道例如
names of our our endpoints or our sample
我们的端点或样本的名称
data like the sequel overall the web
像整个网络续集这样的数据
stopped endpoints for application
停止应用端点
otherwise we got a we know we got away
否则我们得到了一个我们知道我们已经离开了
with not having to configure much at all
根本不需要配置太多
you know this is we need to those
你知道这是我们需要的
valuables but if this was all spring
贵重物品，但是如果这是整个春天
bloomers it is and well yeah just thing
灯笼裤，是的，是的
last it would be as cool as a my
最后它会像我的一样酷
excitement should need you to believe um
兴奋应该需要你相信
it's actually quite a bit more right so
实际上还可以，所以
what does it mean to get a you know what
知道是什么意思
it mean
它的意思是
application
应用
production light to quote the epic tome
引用史诗巨著的生产光
release it feature complete does not
释放它功能齐全不
equal production ready right there's a
平等的生产准备好了
quite a bit that has to be done to get
必须做的很多事情
something out
东西出来
get something production ready and a lot
准备好生产的东西
of that is management it's it's
这就是管理，是
monitoring it's inside method its
监视它的内部方法
analysis its it's all this stuff and
分析所有这些东西，
Springwood has all that stuff in spades
Springwood拥有所有这些东西
so we're going to go ahead and take a
所以我们要继续
look at some laptop right now designed
看一些现在设计的笔记本电脑
to promote visibility intensive and to
提升能见度
support you know the you know
支持你知道你知道
all right these kinds of things that
好吧，这些事情
teams spent a long time getting right
团队花了很长时间才能正确
and should just be out of the box now
并且应该现在就开箱
it's the route okay let's look at common
这是好的路线，让我们来看一下常见的问题
things let's suppose um I want to see
让我们假设我想看的东西
you know how my application is doing
你知道我的申请情况如何
that if suppose the health of the
如果假设健康
application I can go to the health
我可以去申请健康
endpoint which we didn't have to
我们不需要的端点
configure it's just there if you have
配置它就在那里
the spring boot starter actuator module
弹簧启动启动器执行器模块
on the left on the path map by default
默认情况下位于路径图的左侧
you'll get a default screen here if
您将在此处获得默认屏幕，如果
you're using a sequel JPA stack it'll
您正在使用续集JPA堆栈
get the last known exception if there is
如果存在则获取最后一个已知异常
one and you also get the name provider
一个，你也会得到名字提供者
for example you know for using h2 as the
例如，您知道使用h2作为
database you'll see Walt reflected in
数据库，您将看到Walt反映在其中
the structure that's shown that well
表现得很好的结构
there's another endpoint called metrics
还有另一个端点称为指标
metrics shows you all the requests that
指标会向您显示所有的请求
have been made and their status code so
已经制作好了，其状态码也是如此
for example there's a call to the client
例如打给客户的电话
endpoint portal client one time it has
端点门户客户端一次
fast code of 200 a call to the health
快速拨打200致电健康
endpoint 1 times that's code of 200 if I
端点1倍，如果我是200
go back to the client
回到客户
here
这里
Oh host client refresh refresh refresh
呵呵主机客户端刷新刷新刷新
and then go back here refresh you can
然后回到这里刷新即可
see it reflects how many times you've
看到它反映了你有多少次
done it nine times right this is fine of
做了九次，这很好
course but sometimes you know some some
当然，但是有时候你知道一些
people don't want that directly on a
人们不希望直接在
website they prefer to get at get a more
他们更喜欢访问的网站获得更多
traditional management tool like for
传统的管理工具，例如
example JMX
示例JMX
no mechanism like jnx well turned out
没有像jnx这样的机制
spring boot automatically export some
Spring Boot自动导出一些
stuff by Gen X as well so you just
X世代的东西，所以你只是
launch your launcher jjx console in this
在此启动您的启动器jjx控制台
case J console and sign in and beans or
案例J控制台并登录和bean或
explain framework those and you can look
解释那些框架，你可以看看
at you know a lot of the same stuff that
你知道很多相同的东西
we saw before
我们以前见过
there's the metric seven-point call get
有公制的七点通话
data and you can get this you know the
数据，您可以了解到
same kind of data for of just inside of
内的相同数据
JMX and that if you have ever played
JMX，如果您曾经玩过
with spring is a very very important you
春天对你来说非常重要
know that there's good support for for
知道有很好的支持
example reacting to a change of property
对属性变化做出反应的示例
or clearing data in game X and so on so
或清除游戏X中的数据，依此类推
you want to build some sort of something
你想建立某种东西
that reacts to the stay in any pan there
对停留在任何锅里的反应
usually um but there's more you know not
通常是um，但还有更多您不知道的地方
only does it slice and dice but there's
它只切成薄片，但有
even more so another very very
甚至更多
convenient way to get access to this
方便的方式来访问这个
kind of template we can use the crash of
我们可以使用崩溃的那种模板
shell which is again very easily
壳很容易
supported if you're on the right to put
如果您有权放货，则提供支持
types on the class that um Springwood
在Springwood课堂上的类型
automatically configures it and by
自动配置并通过
default it'll configure a username and
默认情况下，它将配置用户名和
password and it will print out the
密码，它将打印出
password on the shell I've pinned the
我固定的外壳上的密码
password down to a specific word meetup
密码到特定的单词聚会
I did that by specifying a property in
我是通过在
this property file by default spring
默认情况下，此属性文件为spring
boot will look for properties in the
开机会在
file called application up properties or
称为应用程序启动属性的文件或
applicant application that llamo why I
那个llamo的申请人申请我为什么
know assuming you have the a shaky
知道假设你有一个摇摇欲坠
animal library of the class back
班级动物回
this case we're setting the password to
在这种情况下，我们将密码设置为
be yep so we're saying user name is user
是的，所以我们说用户名是用户
for the shell and then meetup is the
对于壳，然后见面是
password um by the way I should mention
密码um，我应该提到
that do you want to know what other
你想知道其他吗
properties can use configure your
属性可以使用配置您的
application there is a very handy end
应用程序非常方便
point called config prompts which shows
名为config提示的点
you for all the beams that are active
您为所有活跃的光束
right now what properties you might
现在你可能会拥有什么属性
stipulate or specify to override things
规定或指定优先事项
for example so if I wanted to override
例如，如果我想覆盖
the the server port the port on which
服务器端口上的端口
the embedded Tomcat that we're using
我们正在使用的嵌入式Tomcat
serves as web application with me I
与我一起作为Web应用程序
might specify server duck port in an in
可能在in中指定服务器鸭端口
the property file and then specify 80 81
属性文件，然后指定80 81
or some other port and in that case that
或其他端口，在这种情况下
will be honored right so this is a very
将会很荣幸，所以这是一个非常
convenient way to override the default
覆盖默认值的便捷方法
behavior without we program everything
没有我们编写所有程序的行为
yourself we get another example boot
你自己，我们得到另一个示例启动
deferring to you but providing useful
顺服您但提供有用
sensible default otherwise so now with
明智的默认设置，否则现在与
that said we've established that we have
那说明我们已经确定我们有
a shell room it's listening in report
报告中正在监听的空壳室
2000 username is user and hang on
2000用户名是user并挂起
localhost the password is me up enter
本地主机密码是我输入
and we jumped into this crash a shell
然后我们跳进了这场崩溃
there are few commands the supposed to
应该有几个命令
be all you issue help it'll just take
是您发出的所有帮助，只需要
forever the very first time but of
永远是第一次，但是
course subsequent runs are very quick
当然，后续运行非常快
lots of good stuff in here you can for
很多好东西，你可以在这里
example an endpoint list will you know
您知道的示例端点列表
show you all the endpoints we can invoke
向您展示我们可以调用的所有端点
one of them so for example invoke
其中之一，例如调用
that what a cetera you can use JVM type
那你可以使用JVM类型
for the i/o JVM system to get
让I / O JVM系统获取
information about system for example one
有关系统的信息，例如一个
foam
泡沫
you can do a system prop LS to see all
你可以做一个系统道具LS来查看所有
the environment variables you know the
您知道的环境变量
system that give properties and I've
提供属性的系统，我已经
enumerated all that tab completion is
列举了所有制表符补全是
very nice here whooping it metrics again
非常好，再次将其指标
we saw that earlier but it's again
我们之前看到了，但是又来了
they'll be shell the enumeration of
他们将壳枚举
which requests were made and so on by
提出了哪些要求，依此类推
the way you'll notice that we're using
您会注意到我们正在使用的方式
here counters and gauges this is a
在这里计数器和仪表这是一个
subsystem that spring loop provides that
弹簧循环提供的子系统
you can contribute to as well you can
你也可以做出贡献
enable data at one and indeed you can
一次启用数据，实际上您可以
control how that data is published and
控制数据的发布方式，以及
look at that in a second
一秒钟看看
one of my favorite end points is of
我最喜欢的终点之一是
course is dashboard it shows you Java
当然是仪表板，它向您展示Java
top if you want will pop and then the
如果需要，将弹出，然后
memory on the bottom right here for
右下角的内存
example well by the left on the right
右边的左边很好的例子
you notice that we're using meta space
您注意到我们正在使用元空间
the Java 8 feature it's the successor to
Java 8功能是它的后续产品
the much-hated
讨厌的人
crimson space that we had before and
我们之前拥有的深红色空间和
some minute face to the Java 8
Java 8的一些细节
equivalent but if you had a Java 78 then
等效，但是如果您有Java 78，则
this would show you
这会告诉你
pungent instead okay very very
辛辣而不是好非常非常
convenient all this is secure you can
方便，所有这些都是安全的，您可以
defer if you like to bring security
推迟如果您想带来安全
stack if you wanted to otherwise but
堆叠，如果你想否则
again benefit we're just using the
再次受益，我们只是在使用
password in the username that our we've
我们拥有的用户名中的密码
specified ok so that's not bad we got a
指定确定，所以还不错，我们得到了
lot there I mentioned earlier that you
我之前提到过很多你
can override or anything like that let's
可以覆盖或类似的东西，让我们
suppose for example that you wanted to
例如，假设您想
override how matrix are published and
覆盖矩阵的发布方式以及
let's also suppose that you want to
我们还假设您想要
override what it meant for an
覆盖它对
application to be healthy well I want to
我想要健康的申请
change the applications definition of
更改的应用程序定义
help I want I want to use my own
帮助我想要使用自己的
definition because I have a better idea
定义，因为我有一个更好的主意
of what it means where my applications
我的应用程序在哪里意味着什么
help them all right so I'm going to go
好的，请帮助他们，我要走了
ahead and contribute a health indicator
前进并贡献健康指标
type and again I'm using a lambda
输入，然后再次使用lambda
expression satisfy the functional
表达满足功能
interface interface that is health
界面健康
indicator I'm saying try and connect the
指标，我是说尝试连接
mungo if I didn't work return the string
mungo，如果我不工作，则返回字符串
okay otherwise return failure and of
好，否则返回失败
course you can easily tie this to
当然，您可以轻松地将其绑定到
something like New Relic ER or Nagios or
例如New Relic ER或Nagios或
whatever in our monitoring tools usual
通常在我们的监控工具中
is metal work and then
是金属制品，然后
so I want to configure metrics I want to
所以我想配置指标
configure how the metrics are published
配置如何发布指标
so I can VIN weld them in this case I
所以我可以在这种情况下VIN焊接它们
want to visualize them using something
想要用某种东西形象化他们
like that
像那样
graphite the metric system at Springwood
石墨在Springwood的公制
provides you with and it's powerful and
为您提供了强大的功能
very expressive but again we're not
很有表现力，但我们又不是
trying to win that the wheel ever
试图赢得方向盘
possibly provide integrations with
可能提供与
existing to go one very very popular
现有去很受欢迎
tool chest for graph for metrics is
指标图的工具箱是
something by German named Kota Heil the
德国人叫Kota Heil的东西
Kota Heil metrics library he it's
Kota Heil指标库
library from the Yammer if memory serves
Yammer提供的库，如果有内存的话
so DM we're going to do it here is when
所以DM我们要在这里做
you register a custom configuration
您注册自定义配置
class I'm going to publish our register
课程我要发布我们的注册信息
a graphite reporter beam and this is
石墨记者光束，这是
going to publish what's happening in our
将要发布我们正在发生的事情
application to graphite which is a
在石墨中的应用
graphing and analysis tool right fair
图形和分析工具权利公平
warning it's not for the faint of heart
警告这不是为了胆小的人
you have not set it up before I don't
你没有我没有设置
know bring some whiskey or something
知道带些威士忌或其他东西
it'll take a little out
会花一点时间
now with that open
现在打开
you
您
well lost your audio again for a second
再次失去音频
everybody
大家
I'll show you that but we needed to be
我会告诉你，但我们需要
up for a minute so uh yeah back up to
等一分钟，所以嗯，回到
senses the law do cut out again sorry
感觉法律确实再次取消了抱歉
sure now we have a custom health
确定现在我们有一个自定义健康
endpoint right this is our custom health
端点对，这是我们的自定义健康
endpoint that defers to the health
健康的终点
indicator that we've just installed
我们刚刚安装的指示器
again if we're if I were to kill MongoDB
再一次，如果我们要杀死MongoDB
this would reflect that immediately
这将立即反映出
which is good for monitoring right you
这对监视您很有好处
will want your pager to go out as soon
希望您的传呼机尽快出去
as possible I'll do that in a minute but
我会在一分钟内做到
before we do that let's create some
在我们这样做之前，我们先创建一些
traffic and some impressions so we can
交通和一些印象，我们可以
go to graphite let's see an axon right
去石墨让我们看看轴突吧
so again graphite is installed on the
因此再次将石墨安装在
system it's not easy to install but
系统不容易安装，但
we've got it done on my computer it's
我们已经在我的电脑上完成了
running on port 990 and you can see it
在990端口上运行，您可以看到它
is already been published to it from our
已经从我们的出版物中发布了
Spring Doge application
春季总督申请
and you can see all the em sort of usual
您会看到所有类似的
suspects that we saw earlier reflected
我们之前看到的嫌疑人反映了
here right so our goal
在这里，所以我们的目标
zoom in or I can die well I can see the
放大，否则我会死的很好，我可以看到
data here this is a default graphite
数据这里是默认石墨
install those Xavier can be a graphite
安装那些Xavier可以是石墨
client which is far more reactive if you
客户，如果您，则反应会更快
will called giraffe it's an html5 based
将称为长颈鹿，这是一个基于html5的
client so you just take the html5 page
客户端，所以您只需要html5页面
back it into a browser and there you go
将其备份到浏览器中，然后就可以了
you can actually see you some of the
你实际上可以看到你的一些
database stair-stepped in this is all
数据库楼梯就此而已
data this represents what we've been
代表我们经历过的数据
publishing from the web application
从Web应用程序发布
itself right so you can configure how
本身是正确的，所以您可以配置
this data looks and what it does but it
该数据看起来及其作用，但它
expensive to say this is very very
昂贵地说这是非常非常
convenient stuff this is very useful
方便的东西，这是非常有用的
stuff and helps you react in and plan
东西，并帮助您做出反应并计划
accordingly you can see what happens
因此，您可以看到发生了什么
when your application dips into a too
当您的应用程序也陷入
much load and so on okay so last trick
这么多的负载，等等，所以最后一个把戏
let's go ahead and kill MongoDB fairly
让我们继续并杀死MongoDB
well Mongo we knew you well okay go back
蒙哥，我们知道你很好，回去吧
to the application
到应用程序
to get error right our customer health
正确解决客户的健康问题
indicator tells you no it worked it
指示器告诉您不起作用
knows how to a to warm that our system
知道如何温暖我们的系统
is down so the login if SP and echo out
已关闭，因此如果SP和echo退出，则登录
there or or look at the JX as well
在那里，或者也看看JX
all those endpoints would not reflect
所有这些端点都不会反映
that there's an error something is wrong
有错误的地方出了问题
again we could have returned a full-on
再次，我们本来可以返回完整版
JSON object but we just returned almost
JSON对象，但我们几乎返回了
in token okay
总的来说还可以
so um I alluded to it earlier but
所以我早些提到
there's a couple deployment options you
您有几个部署选项
can use by default we're using an
可以默认使用
embedded in memory or sorry embedded
嵌入内存或抱歉
Pachi Tomcat 7 you can use embedded
可以使用嵌入式Pachi Tomcat 7
jetty if you liked this video 8 or 9
码头，如果你喜欢这部影片8或9
you simply exclude the Tomcat starter
您只需排除Tomcat入门者
and then install the jetty starter and
然后安装码头启动器和
voila we will defer to that instead if
瞧，如果
you'd like to package up your
你想打包你的
application for deployment consider all
部署申请考虑所有
the places there way standalone you know
你知道那里独立的地方
traditional tom cat or even a app you
传统的汤姆猫甚至您的应用
know EE application server but
知道EE应用服务器但是
absolutely there's absolutely no reason
绝对没有理由
you couldn't it's for fine
你不可能很好
by default you have a fat jar this thing
默认情况下，您有一个胖子罐子
booth this is an ideal choice for cloud
展位，这是云计算的理想选择
environments like a platform as a
像平台这样的环境
service where they favor the bring your
他们喜欢的服务带给您
own container model all this time we've
一直以来我们都有自己的容器模型
been relying on the default that spring
一直依赖那个春天的默认值
we provide we've been looking at we
我们提供我们一直在寻找我们
didn't have to configure any of the
不必配置任何
spring data set example we don't have to
spring data 集的例子，我们不必
configure spring MVC we don't have to
配置Spring MVC，我们不必
configure a lot of that in constructor
在构造函数中配置很多
that's possible through the magic of
这可以通过魔术来实现
Java configuration of auto configuration
Java配置自动配置
so when the application starts up we see
因此，当应用程序启动时，我们看到
the at Nemo auto configuration
Nemo自动配置
annotation that till spring boot to
直到 spring boot 的注释
stand the plat path and to find all
站在平台上，找到所有
spring dubbed factories files in all the
春天被称为工厂文件
jars that have them and then to activate
有它们的罐子然后激活
the classic ruled by what property so I
经典由什么财产统治，所以我
think I can show you one here screen
想我可以在这里显示一个画面
boot
开机
okay
好的
later there
后来在那里
and bring that one
并带来那个
I don't spring blue all these they gave
我不给他们所有这些都染成蓝色
it good so many ants bring that
好多蚂蚁带来的
factories and you can see here with that
工厂，你可以在这里看到
org spring formal food auto-configure ah
org春季正式食品自动配置啊
enable auto configuration equal and then
启用自动配置等于，然后
a comma-separated list of fully
以逗号分隔的完整列表
qualified class names Java configuration
合格的类名Java配置
class names and you might be wondering
类名，您可能想知道
what you know that doesn't sound good
你知道那听起来不好
right I don't want I don't all these
对，我不要所有这些
different classes to be activated when
何时激活不同的类
my application starts up and thankfully
我的应用程序启动了，谢天谢地
they're not right so these these
他们不对，所以这些
configuration classes build on am on a
配置类建立在上午
job and a spring for feature called add
工作和称为add的功能的春天
conditional which lets you conditionally
有条件的让你有条件
activate the configuration class think
激活配置类思考
of it as a much more broad spectrum much
它的范围更广
more general-purpose facility like the
更通用的设施，例如
profile facility in fact the proof the
简介工具实际上是
profiles mechanism has been actively
配置文件机制一直很活跃
made a specialization of additional
做了额外的专业化
mechanism that's been introduced in
引入的机制
spring forward so we can use at
向前发展，所以我们可以在
conditional to say based on some
有条件地说
conditions and it complete our control
条件，它完成了我们的控制
that you can combine oil based on some
你可以结合一些基础油
condition activate the beam or B tags of
条件激活光束或B标签
that condition in this case I'm even you
在这种情况下，我什至是你
can even say don't activate this class
甚至可以说不要激活该课程
if the rabbits template and channel type
如果兔子模板和频道类型
I'm not on the clasp at all right in
我完全没有掌握
this case these are not in the class but
在这种情况下，这些不在课堂上，但
I can't click on this so this class will
我无法点击此课程，因此该课程将
never get activated which is good right
永远不会被激活，这是对的
I don't want rabbitmq infrastructure to
我不希望Rabbitmq基础架构
be created and loaded if I have a
如果我有一个创建和加载
gravity on the path path and I have no
路径上的重力，我没有
use for my application so again we're
用于我的应用程序，所以我们再次
doing it as much as we can based on
尽我们所能
what's happening babe if and cues in the
宝贝发生了什么事
environment ok
环境还可以
a couple of things before we go there
我们去那里之前的几件事
already many other projects using spring
已经有许多其他使用Spring的项目
spring but-- spring XD welcome to the
春天，但是-XD春天欢迎您
data plan little bit a little bit while
数据计划一点点
ago and that's been rebase to sit on top
以前，这已经变基为坐在最前面
of booth j hipsters a Galman which is a
展位j赶时髦的人加尔曼
node.js ecosystem code generation Swiss
node.js生态系统代码生成瑞士
Army knife tool type thing and there's a
军刀工具类型的东西，有一个
technology called a hipster which build
被称为时髦的技术
on that on that code generation thing
关于那个代码生成的东西
and generate some string good
并生成一些好的字符串
applications the Vaadin component
应用Vaadin组件
framework has a nice working loop
框架具有良好的工作循环
integration and in my my humble opinion
整合和我的拙见
it's actually a nice way to use bottom
这实际上是使用底部的好方法
and bottom by itself activity 2 has won
并靠活动2赢得了胜利
numerous people if you read the you can
很多人，如果你读了你可以
spring for example let's round up I put
以春天为例，让我们总结一下
together every Tuesday there's usually
每个星期二在一起通常
just lots of posts about people who are
关于人的很多帖子
using boot and it allowed in some cases
使用启动，它在某些情况下允许
moved in my application local to boot
移动到本地应用程序以启动
and week and it results been a net
和一周，结果是一个净额
reduction in code I mentioned all this
减少代码我提到了所有这一切
and I should mention also that boot just
我还要提一下开机
went one point Ogier a couple weeks ago
几周前Ogier一分
so all these things I've just mentioned
所以我刚才提到的所有这些事情
are people who are very very earnest and
是非常非常认真的人，
very very impressed with it embraced it
对它的印象非常深刻
early on and they're in the rest and
早，他们在其余，
stable or movable um people in the
稳定或可移动的人在
community like mat label or blogging
垫子标签或博客等社区
about it so lots of people are very
关于这一点，很多人都非常
excited about this technology wrote a
对此技术感到兴奋的是写了一篇
common question we get is what about
我们得到的常见问题是
live reloading of classes and templates
实时重载类和模板
like in Grails in Grail that features
就像在Grail中的Grails中
enabled critical bring loaded we support
已启用关键支持，我们支持
the same thing if you take the vector
如果取向量也一样
equation you can use spring loaded with
可以使用弹簧加载的方程式
boot I mentioned earlier that you can
我前面提到的引导，您可以
use by default swing boot will check for
默认使用秋千启动将检查
properties at a property file called
属性文件中的属性
application up properties or
应用属性或
applications that Yamma
Yamma的应用
of course you can register a custom
当然，您可以注册自定义
property values and you have property
财产价值，你有财产
fourth mechanism both or whatever there
第四种机制
is a particularly nice groovy innovation
是一个非常好的常规创新
swing boot is a command-line tool that
Swing Boot是一个命令行工具，
you can get if you do boo install spring
你可以得到如果你做嘘安装弹簧
Zenon
泽农
for example it's a a tool that you know
例如，这是一个您知道的工具
spares you even the border plate you
甚至为您节省了边界板
know public static void main the four
知道公共静态无效主体四
line in a post I coordinate application
我协调申请的帖子中的行
twenty points they have the right order
他们有正确的顺序二十分
even that can go right now right with
即使这样现在也可以
the spring of command line tool for busy
忙碌的命令行工具的春天
code there's also an event subsystem it
代码还有一个事件子系统
builds on top of the application couple
建立在应用程序对之上
event mechanism that's available and
可用的事件机制
that's been available in Springs and
在Springs和
stay one and basically we boot uses it
留一个，基本上我们引导使用它
to publish sort of lifecycle events that
发布某种生命周期事件
you might want to be aware of more high
您可能想知道更多
level level ones like for example if
等级等级，例如
somebody authenticates with a spring
有人用弹簧鉴定
stick very principle you can get a
坚持非常原则，你可以得到一个
notification they can get an event
通知他们可以获得事件
published and that's stuff in you know
发表，你知道的东西
is specific and unique to boot um I want
对于我想要的启动是特定且唯一的
to I want to
我想
attention to these two Twitter handles
注意这两个Twitter句柄
they've hired celebrities with co-leads
他们已经与联合领导一起聘请名人
people that started spring booth I think
我认为春季展位开始的人们
they're rock stars super super people
他们是摇滚明星超级超级人
and even real Mensch is a knife I just
甚至真正的Mensch都是我的刀
wanted to say thanks very much for an
非常想感谢您
amazing pathology and for supporting me
惊人的病理学和对我的支持
in this talk as well so and I worked on
在这次演讲中，我也致力于
the code for example I am and remain a
该代码例如我是，并保持
Starbucks man at Starbucks man on
星巴克男人在星巴克男人
Twitter and I am as always your humble
Twitter和我一如既往的谦虚
servants oh don't don't hesitate to
仆人哦，不要犹豫
reach out and care discussion there if
伸出手并关心那里的讨论
you want the code it's on github and of
你想要的代码在github和
course don't hesitate to I got the tux
当然不要犹豫，我穿了晚礼服
and everything else and with that I'll
还有其他一切，我会
turn it back to you guys for questions
把问题转给你们
so bazooms OD has been very patient he
所以bazooms OD非常耐心
asked a question while back on uh right
回来时问了一个问题
around 2:20 or 30 minutes ago he was
大约2:20或30分钟前，他
curious well where the part of the code
很好奇代码的哪一部分
that is actually calling the rest
实际上是在叫其他人
service was that's in that JavaScript
服务就是那个JavaScript
code that we looked at in the web Bible
我们在网络圣经中看到的代码
so yeah we enabled an html5 that
是的，我们启用了html5
meatball thing and we had another bit
肉丸的事，我们还有一点
then actually a gets a notification from
然后实际上是从收到通知
WebSockets all that from script poni you
WebSockets从脚本中获取所有这些
can actually see it here swing those web
实际上可以在这里看到它摆动那些网络
as I mentioned earlier but we split out
正如我之前提到的，但我们分开了
the client-side artifacts with html5
html5的客户端工件
templates the dogs kitchen all that
模板狗厨房
split it up when modeling with
在建模时将其拆分
server-side by Java bits or in a
通过Java位或在服务器端
different one and we just thanks to
不同的，我们只感谢
spring boot and spring mu smooth expose
spring boot 和春天亩顺利暴露
all the assets that are in the web side
网站上的所有资产
through the through the application of
通过应用
you know India and the rest api so these
你知道印度和其他API，这些
JavaScript
的JavaScript
assets that's where all this stuff is
资产就是所有这些东西所在
all the rest calls all the stuff is in
所有其余的东西都在里面
this job's the poach number
这份工作是水煮人数
got it and you said you were using
知道了，你说你在用
WebSocket for that so that when you drag
WebSocket，以便当您拖动时
the photo it would immediately kind of
照片会立即
you know ping ping the reload reload
你知道ping ping重新加载
trigger the ring that exactly
完全触发环
that's website report it's going for me
那是网站报告，适合我
okay and that is an important point by
好的，这很重要
the way everything we're doing here you
我们在这里所做的一切的方式
can already do with spring well actually
实际上已经可以很好地处理弹簧
a lot of the management and monitoring
很多管理和监控
bits but everything we're doing here is
有点，但是我们在这里要做的是
building on top of technologies that are
建立在以下技术之上
already available but again the goal is
已经可用，但目标仍然是
to really really make this simple so it
真的很简单
it should just be very easy to pull in
它应该很容易插入
websites and the polling rest in the
网站和投票站位于
corn data electable yep
玉米数据可选
great oh and then percent
太好了，然后百分比
bassam had this M asam please hear me
巴萨姆有这个阿萨姆，请听我说
from pronouncing your name incorrectly I
从不正确地念出你的名字我
had one more question he was curious how
还有一个问题，他很好奇
to access embedded databases like h2 for
访问诸如h2之类的嵌入式数据库
example I think you were using Mongo on
例如，我认为您在使用Mongo
this one but um you know it should be
这个，但嗯，你知道应该是
trivial to work with an in-memory
在内存中工作微不足道
database I think yeah so by default if
我认为是数据库，所以默认情况下
you have h2 on a class path actually if
你实际上在类路径上有h2
you have h2 on the class path and absent
您在课程路径上有h2且没有
any other explicitly considered javac
任何其他明确考虑的javac
sequel data source spring route will
续集数据源春季路线将
create and invent h2 database for you
为您创建和发明h2数据库
same thing for Derby or for H sequel you
对于Derby或H续集，您也一样
have the requisite libraries on the
在具有必要的库
class path and you don't explicitly
类路径，而您没有明确
configure a data source things it'll
配置数据源的事情
look great one for you because it senses
为你看起来很棒，因为它感觉
that you want one then why would you
你想要一个然后为什么你会
have the library and the class path we
有图书馆和上课的路
didn't join but just by putting it on
没有加入，只是穿上
the class path boot
类路径启动
configures it for you automatically Wow
自动为您配置它哇
indeed that it's really friend else but
确实，这真的是朋友，但是
again it'll back off if you configure
再次，如果您配置
yourself a little and you can use the
自己一点，你可以使用
spring profound it's a it has one
春天深刻的是它有一个
configuration for dev and Q testing and
开发和Q测试的配置以及
production and you know flowers whatever
生产，你知道花什么
and you once told me that if you put a
你曾经告诉我，如果你放一个
dot sequel file in the right place that
点续集文件在正确的位置
it'll actually make the database for you
它实际上将为您创建数据库
dinner am I remembering that correctly
晚餐我记得正确吗
absolutely so there's a if you put a
绝对如此，如果您放一个
schema that's equal and the fourth main
相等的模式和第四个主要
reason folder it'll load the video on
原因文件夹将在其上加载视频
that if you put a data that sequel and
如果您放置一个续集的数据，
the source main reason order it'll load
将加载的源主要原因顺序
a sequel statements to be dated by Iran
伊朗过时的续集声明
since we're using Mongo I use the
由于我们使用的是Mongo，因此我使用了
repository to programmatically insert
以编程方式插入的存储库
three records into the native but if I
三个记录到本地，但如果我
was using a single database I could just
我正在使用一个数据库
put that a sequel file or that would get
放一个续集文件，否则会得到
run it started Wow so no more wow that's
运行它开始哇，所以没有更多的哇
pretty cool
很酷
okay so we know a lot of people use my
好，所以我们知道很多人都在使用我的
sequel so if that's the use case you
续集，如果这是用例，
just drop your your you know development
放弃你所知道的发展
schema in the sequel file and you're
续集文件中的架构，
done that's pretty cool I don't think
做到那很酷，我不认为
good all right basim thanks I hope you
好吧，好吧，谢谢，我希望你
all can answer your questions on I think
所有人都可以回答我的问题
we're pretty much shut we're pretty much
我们几乎是封闭的，我们几乎是
done we're a little over time folks so
完成了，我们是时间久了的人，所以
thank you so much for joining and
非常感谢您的加入和
Alexandre lino yeah absolutely
Alexandre lino是的，绝对
um just want to let you know we do have
嗯，只是想让你知道我们有
some other cool webinars coming up this
一些其他很酷的网络研讨会
month on if you are around on the 30th
如果您在30日左右，
of this month you can come back and join
这个月的你可以回来加入
Josh again he's going to be joined by
乔希再次他将被加入
Ashley polls from New Relic and they are
来自新遗物的阿什利民意测验
going to talk about how to do web app
要谈论如何做网络应用
Diagnostics on when you're working with
有关何时使用的诊断
web applications where you have like I
像我一样的Web应用程序
sprang back in and a JavaScript
弹回来，并显示JavaScript
front-end which is very common these
这些很常见的前端
days
天
um it is an architecture we've been
嗯，这是我们去过的建筑
espousing and talking about it that the
拥护和谈论它
pivotal and with the spring team for
关键，并与春季团队合作
what two year two plus years now at
现在两年零两年了
least forever in the know uh yeah yeah
至少永远在知道中
no kidding so that'll be on April 30th
别开玩笑了，那就是4月30日
so please join us for that
所以请加入我们
um in fact I'm just going to see if I
嗯，实际上我只是看我是否
can pop the URL for that here into the
可以将此处的URL弹出到
question in control panel on let's see
在控制面板上的问题，让我们看看
oh and Bassam had one other question on
哦，巴萨姆还有一个问题
so let me oh cool actually I'm getting a
所以让我哦，酷，实际上我正在
few more questions come in now on so
现在再来几个问题
Roman
罗曼
Ivanenko asks if I use schema.org and I
伊万年科问我是否使用schema.org和
detect the schema already exists ah so
检测架构已经存在啊
the the way the so this is actually a
的方式，所以这实际上是一个
spring JDBC mechanism and it's using the
Spring JDBC机制，它使用
one of the data source analyzer pipes
数据源分析器管道之一
and it's it can be programmed to to
它可以被编程为
Halon error but by default if you have
哈龙错误，但默认情况下（如果有）
an error after examples we try and
尝试执行示例后出现错误
execute it as the VL statement that that
将其作为VL语句执行
fails because that table already exists
失败，因为该表已经存在
it'll just skip it right so you can you
它只会正确跳过它，因此您可以
can usually just go ahead and blend pine
通常可以继续搅拌松木
excellent any that could already just
优秀的任何已经可以
just ignore it but you kind of detective
只是忽略它，但你有点侦探
a table already exists that's up to your
一个已经存在的表格取决于您
particular vendors you know GDL
您知道GDL的特定供应商
supported syntax there's no standard way
支持的语法没有标准方法
right
对
like for example in and my people you
例如喜欢和我的人你
can say if table equals for example
可以说表是否等于
awesome um thanks Josh uh yeah I mean
太棒了，谢谢Josh uh是的
most of the time I would see people
大多数时候我会看到人们
write me their sequel statements to like
给我写他们的续集声明，喜欢
drop the tables first and then create
首先删除表，然后创建
them but that's assuming that you're in
他们，但这是假设你在
a development mode don't have data they
开发模式没有数据
care about right so that's that's just
在乎正确，就是这样
another thought for you running on the
你在跑步上的另一个想法
sim also asked he faced one problem when
sim还问他何时遇到一个问题
you spring booth data JPA with data
您可以在展位数据JPA中添加数据
Mongo in the same project are you
您在同一个项目中的Mongo是您
supposed to use them together
应该一起使用
I don't see why not yeah um I don't know
我不明白为什么不呢嗯我不知道
what the specific problem is but you
具体的问题是什么，但是你
might have some issues with repositories
储存库可能有一些问题
themselves but for example do we just
自己，但例如
want to use the spring dated JPA in a
想要在一个
wall and any manager and you wanted to
墙和任何经理，你想
work with the Mongol templates there
使用那里的Mongol模板
should be example no problem there but
应该是例子，没有问题，但是
there are solutions with two different
有两种不同的解决方案
types of repositories in the same spring
同一春季的存储库类型
up yep um okay well just a quick recap
是的，嗯，好吧，快速回顾一下
so I think we we set a couple questions
所以我认为我们提出了几个问题
in I always like to give priority to
在我总是喜欢优先
those just a quick recap well we are
那些只是快速回顾一下，我们就是
going to be joined Josh on April 30th
将于4月30日加入Josh
for on New Relic on and talking about
在New Relic上谈论
the debugging JavaScript apps front to
调试JavaScript应用程序
back along with the spring backend and
回到春天的后端，
then on April 22nd Mike Milankovitch
然后在4月22日，Mike Milankovitch
from the Eclipse Foundation and Mark
来自Eclipse Foundation和Mark
Lippert our lead on spring pools week is
利珀特在春季泳池周上的领先优势是
going to be talking about a new and
将要谈论一个新的和
exciting project at the Eclipse
Eclipse中令人兴奋的项目
Foundation called project flux on the
基金会称项目通量为
idea that is to start to begin to bridge
开始桥接的想法
the browser based editing experience and
基于浏览器的编辑体验，以及
browser based IDE experience with the
基于浏览器的IDE体验
Eclipse IDE that should be pretty
应当漂亮的Eclipse IDE
interesting something that Michael
有趣的东西，迈克尔
linker which was the executive director
链接器是执行董事
of the foundation you know he brought it
你知道他带来的基础
made a big splash at Eclipse on and
在Eclipse上引起了轰动
something he's particularly interested
他特别感兴趣的东西
in so very cool project and I'm going to
在一个非常酷的项目中，我要
check that out
检查出
ah and we will post the replay of this
啊，我们将发布此重播
salt talk in the next two weeks often we
在接下来的两个星期，我们经常进行盐谈
get to it a lot faster that we'll post
更快地发布它，我们将发布
that at spring do /video and on seems
在春天做/ video等
like a few people had issues with sound
就像少数人在声音方面遇到问题
on this webinar so just apologize for
在此网络研讨会上，只为表示歉意
that not really quite sure what's
不太确定是什么
happening what we'll do a best to figure
发生我们将尽力而为的事情
it out um but in my side a few times
嗯，但在我这边几次
right yeah just a couple but no one's
是的，只有一对，但没人
giving me specific feedback on the
给我有关的具体反馈
specific what they're specifically
具体他们具体是什么
experiencing but yes we will we try to
遇到，但是是的，我们将尝试
take great care care to make sure that
格外小心，以确保
the audio is good and and will well
音频很好，而且会很好
posting a replay of this within two
在两天内发布此内容的重播
weeks off a lot less than that on so
几周比这少得多
with that thank you very much appreciate
对此，非常感谢
everyone's time and hope to see you on a
每个人的时间，希望看到你
future webinar thank you everybody
未来的网络研讨会谢谢大家
Cheers
干杯
you
您